const DATA = [
    {
        question: `What was the United States' first constitution called?`,
        answers: [
            `The Federalist Papers`,
            `The Emancipation Proclamation`,
            `The Declaration of Indepencence`,
            `The Articles of Confederation`
        ],
        correctAnswer: `The Articles of Confederation`
    },
    {
        question: `Who is considered the "Father of the Constitution"?`,
        answers: [
            `George Washington`,
            `Benjamin Franklin`,
            `James Madison`,
            `John Adams`
        ],
        correctAnswer: `James Madison`
    },
    {
        question: `Why was the Constitution written?`,
        answers: [
            `To protect the rights of individuals`,
            `To limit the federal government`,
            `To guarantee local government rights`,
            `All of the above`
        ],
        correctAnswer: `All of the above`
    },
    {
        question: `How many times has the Constitution been amended?`,
        answers: [
            `7`,
            `27`,
            `23`,
            `14`
        ],
        correctAnswer: `27`
    },
    {
        question: `What series of essays were written to support the adoption of the Constitution?`,
        answers: [
            `Common Sense`,
            `The Age of Reason`,
            `The Federalist Papers`,
            `The Articles of Confederation`
        ],
        correctAnswer: `The Federalist Papers`
    },
    {
        question: `Laws for the United States are made by:`,
        answers: [
            `Congress`,
            `The Senate`,
            `The Supreme Court`,
            `The President`
        ],
        correctAnswer: `Congress`
    },
    {
        question: `Under the Constitution, the longest a president can serve is:`,
        answers: [
            `8 years`,
            `10 years`,
            `6 years`,
            `12 years`
        ],
        correctAnswer: `10 years`
    },
    {
        question: `What are the first words of the preamble to the Constitution?`,
        answers: [
            `We hold these truths to be self-evident`,
            `Four score and seven years ago`,
            `When in the course of human events`,
            `We the people of the United States`
        ],
        correctAnswer: `We the people of the United States`
    },
    {
        question: `When was the Constitution signed?`,
        answers: [
            `July 4, 1776`,
            `April 12, 1782`,
            `Sept 17, 1787`,
            `Dec 8, 1791`
        ],
        correctAnswer: `Sept 17, 1787`
    },
    {
        question: `Why was the Ninth Amendment added to the Constitution?`,
        answers: [
            `To give congress the power to print money`,
            `Because the framers wanted to make clear that basic rights were guaranteed event if they were not stated specifically`,
            `To give women the right to vote`,
            `Because the English Bill of Rights had to have 10 parts`
        ],
        correctAnswer: `Because the framers wanted to make clear that basic rights were guaranteed even if they were not stated specifically`
    },
]; 

 